welcome to the stola the stoah is a
digital campfire where we go here and
dialogue about what matters most at the
night's edge what's happening now
mmm check-ins I feel like a calm
deadness
and then there's maybe 5% nervousness
and a feeling of grounded power so
welcome to the stoah I am the Stewart
Peter Lindbergh and this is a place
where we Co hear and dialogue about what
matters most at the knife's edge of this
moment and today we're gonna discuss two
memes or two phrases that sort of
emerged out of the stoah one is steel
the culture and the other is seduced the
culture and rave and I are gonna have a
conversation and then we're gonna go
pivot to a group conversation or
activities Raven hasn't more knowledge
about this so I will let Raven kind of
speak a little bit more about that I'm
gonna do a check-in - oh yeah I feel a
little jittery I'm excited to unpack
this and I feel calm okay
so we're gonna talk about these two
ideas that have been floating around
different conversations in the stoechas
they've been thread throughout many of
the discussions that have been happening
here and we thought that we would use
some of the skills that we've learned
from some of the wisdom gym practices
for example Socratic speed-dating to
kind of investigate the possibilities of
these of these ideas so I'm gonna start
by asking Peter about steal the culture
can you tell me where that came from
sure so my good buddy John rebecky
I think the first week that the stoah
was launched over a month ago now he
came and did a session on the meaning
Kairos sort like a meaning opportunity
that we have during this endemic and we
sourced the
questions to the collective intelligence
of the group when someone asks like a
wonderful question I can't remember who
what it was but I think it was Joe and
John just like when I'll fire you got
passionate and he said he wants to steal
the culture from the people who have
been abusing us for so long and I'm like
who I was delicious and something about
it is really really resonated with me
this phrase steal the culture so that's
where it originated from and then my
journal entries and then sort of in
these sessions we've been mentioning it
here and there and it became sort of the
unofficial till you came along or even
it became like one part the unofficial
motto of sort of the spirit of this
group or the project of the stoah and
even the key or the dawn that guy who
does this meaning wave music he's gonna
like make a song out of that that clip
so there's actually gonna be like a
theme song now for this though which is
pretty cool that's the the origin story
of steal the culture yeah so you had
this like moment right where this this
kind of like insight came about this
handle and you've had this opportunity
to kind of chip away at like what that
might mean it's been brought into like
the community space where we've talked
about different elements of what that
might mean how are you related to it
over time and how are you relating to it
now yeah yeah and so thinking this
through slowly there's this like I don't
think we have a culture right now I
think we have a cult at large and our
culture the cultural artifacts that get
created seem to me to be a service of
ego to prop up our ego and I think true
culture keeps ego in check sort of
polices it so everyone has a healthy ego
I think that's the basis of true
community true communitas and so when I
hear steal the culture I'm inspired to
make that switch for making culture and
service of ego and to make culture keep
you going check and so in the stoah I
feel real communitas real communities is
bubbling up in our wisdom Jim and our
various we space authentic relating
practices and I feel kind of a deep
kinship and bond with people
and just like for example we had
something called I'm not gonna be like I
kind of want to reinvent stoicism or
give it some like soul because I think
modern still movement lost its soul or
never had soul in the first place though
that'd be my argument and so just like
like how do we practice those ISM let's
be creative here there's this event on
Saturday run by my boy Tyson called
freestyling through a pandemic and we
just saw he plays a beat and we start
freestyle rapping with no script in mind
and if you try to engineer something in
advance you can sound like an idiot
great but you just let the words flow
out and you just feels cringe or you
feel like stupid but if you push through
that then actually beauty comes out and
you actually feel connection and we had
like a lot when I was in there was like
ten people the room was all flowing to
the music just looking stupid together
and it felt beautiful so that's the
psycho technology with Ricky's called
the psycho technology our practice that
allows community to build so we're not
we didn't record this may there's an
artifact making album so we get like hit
500 licks or licks likes the other stuff
we're afraid you slip they're delicious
but so yeah so that is sort of the
spirit I don't know if I answer your
questions oh oh yeah yeah I think
definitely part of it I see that there I
was getting an image of like the the
churches of the future we're like
instead of singing out of a great book
we're like freestyle rapping do we have
like existential dance parties here you
know we've got a lot of cool shit so
it's like all that stuff is in curtain
like Epictetus is don't explain your
philosophy and body it it so how do we
embody it well the star is a place right
that's what the the name is does it
speak to a place where the Stoics come
together yeah originally the original
Stoics got their name from a stoic okay
Lee which meant painted porch and so
Zeno the original stoic you just hung
around and people started hanging around
with them and they started
philosophizing and then so they got the
name Stoics because of that and so
that's the same spirit of this sort of
digital campfire is that we're just Co
hearing together and dialoguing but
what's most important at the nice edge
yeah so I think another element of like
what I saw emerging in the Congress
around steal the culture was maybe a
question about whether or not it was
kind of in maybe kind of masculine or a
wrongful spirit you know the idea of
stealing as being something that's maybe
something we would even consider the
others to be doing so I think in some
ways that was how the the beginning of
seduced the culture what that was like
yeah so let me just take the question of
role away from you know I I would be the
questioner and just the preface at
though yes there's sort of like a
masculine almost a fuck you energy to
steal the culture that kind of like has
that to me is sort of righteous do mos
but if you just like have it sort of not
complemented by something a little bit
more archetypical feminine then I think
it could be kind of comic book ish so
that's when you when we were talking at
this was thing a couple weeks ago called
emancipate the daemon session you just
came up with seduce the culture knows
that all something's here so my question
to you Raven is what do you what do you
mean or what did you mean when you mean
when you said seduced a culture yeah I
think in many ways like just like your
experience there was this kind of like
sometimes you just say something and it
rings and I I think I've had a similar
process and also there's a way in which
like it was a call in response right so
like there was steal the culture and
that set up a kind of structure kind of
orientation but it was incomplete in
some way I needed something to be
responded to and I think that that's
also very much in line with this kind of
like architect or feminine and seduce
the culture I think was to speak to the
element of being in inviting or to work
indirectly in order to draw people to
you and much of the way that a fire
draws people you know the fire in the
darkness is something that catches your
eye and Orient's you across a landscape
towards the possibility of others and
you're not stealing anyone's fire too
around the campfire but I don't know the
way that I've been thinking about
stealing has been much more along with
like the trickster ology you know that
Alexander bard was bringing right this
idea of a form on the road that takes
many names and you know as your as your
journey
I mean I'm gonna use this metaphor just
cuz it's so useful you have something
valuable to you you know you have you
have something with you something of
home and in that in that way you have
true wealth but you meet someone on the
road and they're like hey why don't you
trade the thing that you love for
something that I could give you and you
know that thing they're like hey yeah
it'll be great it'll give you returns
everyday it'll make your walk so much
easier and you trade the thing that you
have for this thing that the other
person has and then you realize that
it's fake and I think that that's what's
happening right now
like we're realizing the thing that
we've traded is fake it's cheap
abundance and when crisis hits cheap
abundance doesn't bring people together
that's the thing we've actually traded
for it and so I think stealing is a as a
recognition of where we are which is
having had something stolen from us and
we have to we have to steal it back
mmm-hmm yeah I like that and so am I
getting this from what you just said is
that like it's almost like a Trojan
horse or bait-and-switch you got to you
got to play the spectacled game or in
Gaeta bores notion of respectability I
play that enough so really that the
trickster ology piece like to really
steal the culture you need to at least
pretend to seduce it yeah I think so and
I also think like there's an element of
like seduction that's about signaling
like there's an element of it it's like
I'm in direct communication with the
outside and transmitting things across
distances and like we have to mediate
through this medium that has a lot of
different
characters involved in the way that it
acts and behaves like the algorithms
that we live with in order to signal to
one another of honest like you no
intention to be in community are
corrupted and so you have to move
through the medium of the spectacle but
to do so is to invite a lot of other
characters into your communication and
this create I mean Daniel Stockton
burger talks about this in terms of the
war on sense making right like he talks
about this distortion in our information
ecology so there is true signal there
are communities and I think you know
John rabe is going to talk about this
this this week there are communities who
are transmitting clear signals to one
another and in times of crisis they're
able to like Milan ate those connections
that they already have in order to flow
resources between one another but you
know the infrastructure that you're
building is through online platforms
because we're decentralized you know
we're all over the world and when you
investigate and you use the tools of
this domain you also risk you know
getting lost in all the noise right
right and it's coming to mind is sort of
my previous analysis on the culture war
how in this noosphere the collective
mind or social media internet what you
want to call it there's these minute
medic tribes sort of like philosophies
in the wild that so people have sort of
almost an addiction to memes and
throwing memes at each other sort of
active like propositional violence but
there's like a disembodied quality I
find with that and I don't think you can
win the culture by winning the culture
war we have to do it a different way so
that's where the the trickster comes in
or the seductress and I like the idea of
getting the mimetic tribes in such a way
where we sync them to become the body
tribes well I think this is like the
corrosion heart this is the horse this
is the bait and switch right so we're
taking something that is not valuable
which is like abstract bits just
whatever trash and trading it for
something that is valuable which is
community and like land and fertility
you know and
we're using their worthless currency to
get something of true value you know and
that's that is like we're not winning at
their own game we're trying to win a
different game and actually people
aren't looking over there
I mean Johannes talked about this in his
Heidegger talk we look at nature as
standing reserve and in doing so we've
extracted its resources and we don't see
it for what it is which is like our true
wealth and ability to prosper as a
species and instead we're building
machines and harnessing energy and of
course there's some value to that like
we all live in the value of that but at
the same time it's coming at a trade-off
so I think thinking about all of these
things together we're in a we're in a
complex orientation right now there's a
lot of possibility and there's a lot of
risk and I think that's where the
knife's edges may be seduced scale the
culture like that that line is the
knife's edge yeah because I think it's
just a risk if you kind of lean on one
and not the other and allow them to
balance each other and I'll say this and
maybe we should pivot because there's a
lot of good comments and the chatbox
will pivot to the kind of dialogue
portion but I'll say this it's like I
make the Stoics they're they're kind of
axiomatic truth is live in accordance
with nature and I actually prefer Jordan
halls rebranding of that he didn't
rebrand it first or so I'm just kind of
taking it and putting it on stoicism is
being in right relationship with reality
and you can say being in right
relationship with God or being depending
on your metaphysics but I really like
that being in right relationship with
reality and in being right relationship
with reality we got to be in right
relationship with everything including
the means we use including the you know
all the things that you mentioned about
the land and but it starts with being in
right relationship with each other you
know this moment right here you know and
then that's where community toss is
found and that's where true beauty is
found in my opinion and if we can get
this right I think we're developing an
organic wisdom gym that will promote
this community oz feeling
if we can get this right then I think a
beauty will emerge from it mm-hmm thank
you thank you so we want to give
everybody an opportunity to speak to
each other and let's see depending on
how many people are in the group 29 so
yeah we were thinking maybe groups of
four and in for those of you who haven't
done Socratic speed-dating I'll just
give a little debrief about what that
looks like so typically we would break
into groups of two for the for that
exercise but for this one we'll do four
and for eight minutes you're in this
room with other folks and in this case
we'll be discussing the questions that
have been at the center of this
conversation you go back and forth about
the questions and then we'll come back
and debrief maybe do another one or we
might do an open conversation at that
point as well so I think in terms of
questions if anybody wants to share a
question that they may have in the chat
as a possible resource for others in the
room that's totally fine but I would
just prompt with a few ideas that could
be the point of conversation one would
be just generally what do you think of
seduce what does that mean and steal the
culture do you contest the terminology
are there things that it illuminates and
things that itch that it shields and
what do you think of the things what are
the things that have arisen out of this
conversation so that would be my
provocation and I will put you on the
group's
Peter do you have anything to add uh
no sounds cool good luck everyone
[Music]
can you give me host permissions there
you go thank you
okay so there'll be three to four people
in everyone's room and we'll do it for
eight minutes all right now
everybody back I just want to say that
there were a few people that I saw who
had not joined rooms and I want to
protect wanted to protect like the magic
circle of the group so I just didn't add
you in at that point but you can always
enter the conversation now so I just
wanted to make that clear so Peter do
you want to break up again or do you
want to do a large group discussion
anything yet
how about we just kind of like maybe in
the private chat you can kind of like
reflect on who would you like to speak
in your group and whoever feels called
can maybe speak on behalf of it and what
came up Kyle so that's so much juiciness
came up in ours so uh so we had wond
Donna and Tito and on our group and
Donna was saying how the seduce the
culture it's like you're trying to take
something that you want when you when
you and you're trying to seduce and the
same thing can be said of steel and then
cheeto rightfully said said you know
what we're not trying to steal the
current culture or seduced the current
culture we might be stealing or seducing
like that the metaphysical version of
culture but proposition that was more
accurate is reimagining the culture
which I agreed with then once a like but
there's some like correctness in the
attitude of wanting to steal the culture
and seduce the culture which I thought
was delicious because he's an artist
right as we has that artists attitude
and then Donna said when she felt into
that there's sort of like a pain and
hurt and that that attitude and that
that sentence because you know there's a
longing for culture and and then the
that what came up is sort of like it's a
bait and switch or a Trojan horse you
know like that statement that attitude
that has sort of a correctness about it
could speak to that pain in people who
miss culture and then bring them in and
then as sort of our duty as being good
Stoics to actually have some distance
from that pain so we don't indulge in it
and so we can actually have genuine
communitas here so that was sort of the
organic discussion that happened between
the four of us and there was more but I
thought that was really really rich yeah
interesting
yeah our conversation I think also
danced around what were the limitations
of this view and I think that that was
really valuable in the sense that
dan and Daniel and mimetic we were
talking about attention being maybe a
more tangible tactile way of viewing
what it is that we're actually playing
with because to steal or to seduce
points to a kind of active attention
I mean stealing I mean for it to be
effective is really like you kind of
draw attention to one thing and then
while the attention is being drawn you
take right so attention is being played
with in this case there's a sense that
the terminology I think is kind of
abstract like culture is kind of a term
that a lot of people have a lot of
different interpretations of and also
that steal and seduce are words that
come from the old world the old
vocabulary and that's kind of where we
went with the conversation and I would
definitely invite any of any of those
guys to come and speak for their
thoughts on that case and also for
everybody else if you would like to move
I'm in gallery for you but I'll move to
grid view and then maybe we can bring
our hands and just share what we think
if you'd like to yeah Daniel would you
like to unmute yourself yeah I might
take away from that which I might not
necessarily be representing everybody's
comments well but is that there's almost
like to tactical fronts that we could
take with the idea of the culture and I
what I understood nomadic to say was
that we can think of a culture as
attention which is more tangible but I
like it what Dan said as well which is
culture is kind of like an implicit set
of principles that and the relationships
that share those principles and those
two things have very distinct flavors
although you can kind of see how they're
they're connected so that was my summary
of that conversation does anybody else
want to speak for their group
yeah James our group was heard some of I
think what you or maybe maybe those
Peter who just came back and started
with that where steal and seduced both
kind of imply that this is something
that's been taken and needs to be
returned to rightful owners or other
owners and like you know what is this
Amorphis thing that's been taken and I
can you can you steal it and do we want
to be stealing things like you mentioned
before we broke out and tort and towards
the end we kind of came around to sort
of a you know even seduction as it's
like through all talking before it's
kind of implied it's kind of it's like a
softer maybe like form of stealing you
know there's there's some there's some
nuance to it maybe but it's still
there's still these elements of coercion
and like reducing the agency of whoever
you're you're doing that to so we kind
of talked about seduction in like
seduction is you know certainly welcomed
in some context right like maybe you've
been seduced by someone you were glad
you were seduced by but that still means
that you know you did something you
didn't want to do something there I'd
like to respond to that and I opened up
this proposition of your stress testing
is it's sort of like there's a
difference between the letter of the
mean meme the letter of the mean and the
spirit of the mean all right the letter
of the meme there's like you're
concerned with propositional accuracy
and so steal the culture pseudo so
cultures wrong in that sense it'll be
more like what Tito said reimagining the
culture or something that's more game B
ish but there's sort of like the the
spirit of that mean steal the culture to
seduce the culture that has an actuating
element to it that has to flirt like a
thumos that makes you want to create
something in the world so I could be
wrong but I sensed that having that nice
edge of the balance between having
fidelity to the letter of the meme but
still embracing at least on a felt sense
level that spirit
yeah it could be the case though for for
some those are like rallying calls and
for others there's still a question
about what that actually means and I
think it's important to kind of yeah
like really massage these these ideas
because I think in a way it's like the
terminology is referencing itself in the
sense that the idea I mean what does
seduction arise from what a stealing
come from if we think of those things of
as being virtues that have been
corrupted in some way to become
seduction or become stealing then in a
sense we're trying to steal back and
seduce back stealing and seducing but I
don't know maybe there's something that
punches a little bit harder I'm kind of
interested in breaking out again and
maybe we can discuss that question what
are some other possibilities and I would
ask everybody to have in their mind the
idea that they would maybe come back and
share with the group some of those ideas
while we break out so I will send us a
send us out again
it'll be eight minutes again but with
different people
see him hello hi Peter how's it going
good
we had another really great session
excellent yeah we had a really good
session too we actually came up with
potentially another idea let's hear it
subvert the culture mm-hm
doing well and I would totally invite
anybody from my group to jump in at any
point if you want to clarify some of the
things that you said but one of the
ideas that Sandra was bringing forth was
this idea of like art you know like
really art that just grabs you is
subversive in some way like it doesn't
and subversive in the sense that maybe
it's like not expected and in that way
it it does maybe kind of you could use
the metaphor it steals something from
you or it seduces you or draws you in
but subversion is kind of like the more
value neutral tactical way of getting at
the concept that we may use steel or
seduce to point to interact indirectly
how's that land it lands well I want to
tap in my boy Mac night Billy he said
something similar because he's an artist
in Toronto he just really like
interesting stuff here and I don't know
it back can I put you on the spot and
then talk about beauty and art oh man
yeah sure I think yeah I was just
thinking yeah surprise is huge huge art
and and in subversion for sure and we
were talking about the seductive value
in beauty and that art work is a
philosophy it's a philosophy in what
beauty is and it's a decentralised
philosophy it's something that you feel
through the senses that that isn't
necessarily coming to you in these
ready-made packets it kind of flows
outside of that that's what we're
talking about briefly
any other artists in the room who
resonate with that idea I have another
idea
we're talking about a heart like lately
I think a lot about how four to four
artists missing right now said there's
not a common language to it I think a
good art always came from a culture
where there was a common language people
shared they allowed to create things
like a sort of me message
I was thinking yours about this group
here and I'm sure that everyone here is
very different you know way but was all
here I'm sure that we don't share a
common language at all and I wonder like
I wonder what is this community of
people that have probably some things in
common but also not a lot in common and
what can that community create no way
how can they find language to speak to
each other because that's how that's
what I feel and I don't know I only
didn't a couple of these meetings but
the feeling that I get is that everyone
here is very different but they also
have something that holding us together
so I was thinking about that like how
people who have something in common but
maybe not a lot in common
could create a language together or find
like a sort of meta language to play
with oh yeah
thank you yeah I think that that's
actually one of the big challenges of
our era is that you know there's so many
different kinds of memes that were
attracted to and I think that that was
largely maybe the spirit of the half
that is seduced right like there's an
idea in seduction of attraction and of
signaling and of like that being kind of
how signals are mediated right there's a
kind of perception of distance in the
signal allows you to kind of orient
towards something that's away from you
and in that sense it also attracts you
and I don't know something that that I
was thinking of when you were talking is
you know stealing and seducing and maybe
even some of the other language that
we're using around the stoah has
Christian themes to it in some ways and
I think that certainly there's been a
move that I've seen some philosophers
make towards you explicitly kind of
maybe even reappropriation language that
is Christian in a sense because it it
does have a wide reach I mean you can
give it give that to Christianity and it
has a wide reach and so there's a sense
that there is also it as a religion it's
compounded over time this kind of wisdom
that is not necessarily on the surface
you know it's it's one of those things
it's like how DNA carries around a lot
of extra stuff I think are our stories
that we've carried for a long time have
that as well and you may not realize
that a story in an old book holds a seed
for something else that may get you
through crisis that you don't remember
because it's a one and a 500-year event
or one in a thousand year then rather
than something that happens every year
anyone else feel invited to speak on
behalf of these ideas
I want to help regulate something dan
said in the first chat which is coming
to mind right now where you use the
phrase build and I think it's kind of
like a nice counterpoint to all this
there's seduce there's steal but there's
also build the culture and I wonder if
that brings up anything for anyone yeah
yeah I remember dan said something I
built a stoah about like kind of you
actually used the metaphor of the stoah
of kind of like a can you can you talk
on that again I think that was that was
really brilliant yeah sure yeah I guess
it was the idea we were talking it was
under the the context of building the
store and we were talking and use it
trying to understand what you meant by
scaling so there's scaling it internally
as one instantiation of one digital
campfire and then there's the idea of
building it out as in bunches of digital
campfires across the landscape and so in
the context of a bunch of digital
campfires across the landscape the stoah
is kind of an open forum just a bunch of
pillars and there are no doors or walls
so it's it's kind of an open space
technology where if one wants to one can
jump one can wander across the field and
jump into one stoa or and and then go to
another stoah and and people from other
stoas or other campfires are welcome to
Brewers and vice versa that was kind of
what I was communicating
excellent and then we have mimetic
cheaper job yeah so I wanted to say I
mean we're using afraid steal the
culture it's not exactly the culture
that we want to steal because you know
it's not like we want to become the next
Donald Trump that's not exactly the goal
right but so what we're actually trying
to do is more along the lines of
building the culture but to build it we
have to steal the materials and one of
the important materials is attention
that's a very broad
that's probably brought its way of
saying and I mean authority or
legitimacy those are types of attention
right or sacredness is a type of
attention and so that's what has to be
stolen and my thinking is is that the
the the old style culture like game a or
whatever that's um that's already in
crisis there's a one of Sun Tzu's
precepts or whatever is a loot of
burning building captain my coming out
now you can I'm good yeah so one of loot
a burning building which is that and
there's a nice little phrase uh you know
when if the buildings burning it's not
being guarded so now now is the time to
I just to steal the means of production
now's the time and then build a new
culture
yeah well we are coming into the last
four minutes of our time together I will
open up a moment if anyone else feels
called to bring something final thoughts
ideas something that's been on the tip
of your tongue well if you think of
anything you can put it in the chat for
everybody we'd really love to hear what
people are thinking and in the meantime
Peter would you like to share what we
have coming up this week
yes so I first I just want to say that I
thought that was a really really awesome
session I quite enjoyed it a lot of
insights emerged so I'd like to do more
of these maybe on a weekly basis where
we just sort of philosophize about the
spirit of this project together and just
see what emerges so I'll talk to Raven
about that maybe having a regular thing
about this so if you go to the website
we can talk about upcoming events
actually Raven do you mind just kind of
talking about upcoming like talks cuz
you're gonna be involved that with John
Robin what Matt yeah I just can't
remember the times and everything's
happening but John Robb is gonna be here
he's gonna be talking about the value of
networks in kovat world which I think
kind of relates to a lot of the things
that we've been thinking about here so I
would definitely be excited to see
everybody at that we are I could speak
on that the other ones so that John Rob
one that's at tomorrow at 12 p.m.
Eastern Time
breaking the frame with Travis man he's
doing he's a he's experimenting with
sort of not getting attached to certain
narratives and basically breaking the
frame adopting new and breaking that
framed opting a new one I think that's a
good skill set to have in the liminal
and that's also tomorrow at 7 p.m.
Eastern Time and then on Thursday I'll
plug this one at the wisdom gym we have
about 12 events weekly on the wisdom gym
you can go on the website a shame
breakthrough boot camp with aj bonds
really really good stuff he's a shame
educator about how we can break through
our shame there's another one I wanted
to plug
oh yeah it's not up yet but Daniel maybe
you can talk about the dark stoah that's
gonna occur every Friday I actually
don't know what this Friday's is gonna
be but every Friday we're now doing
basically an exercise of negative
visualization about where the world is
headed and we're having the brilliant
and dangerous Pat Ryan come in to give
us a mind-blowing talk on things such as
CRISPR as art so the technology of
CRISPR and where that's going to be
headed maybe in our lifetimes so I don't
know what this week is going to be but
they're all gonna be they all come with
disclaimers so if you like mildly
traumatized then come to the dark stoah
existential horror for sure I do want to
also talk about your meta game
mastermind if you're called okay cool
let the mystery seduce everyone that be
said I'll uh
Ravin close this out great and on Friday
of course we will have Socratic
speed-dating and it'll be something
different this week a little bit so come
and see what's what's happening with
that Friday at 7:00 Eastern Time hosted
by yours truly and the stoah we see the
stoah here as a as a gift and it's a
gift for everyone freely to use while
we're in this time of crisis and into
the future and if you feel inspired to
give a good a gift to anyone here the
facilitators the stoah please visit us
on the gift economy on the website and I
just want to thank thank you for to
everybody for coming along with the the
breakout rooms and the discussion and
everything you know that was a bit of a
surprise but maybe that's like the metal
level of this we seduced you here to put
you in groups with each other so yeah I
want to say thank you and thank you
Peter for provoking this conversation
yes and thank you Raven for facilitating
it and having that conversation I was
very lovely and thank you everyone for
coming today thank you